http://www.garyhusband.com/pages/privacy

Gary Husband OnlineSkip to content
Close We use cookies to optimize your experience. You agree to our use of cookies by using this website. Learn moreJUST PAY WHAT YOU CAN (OR PAY NOTHING!) FOR TWO OF GARY'S PRACTICAL VIDEOCASTS DURING LOCKDOWN - CLICK HERE FOR DETAILS
Menu
Close Menu
Search
Close SearchKeyword
Search
Home
About
Videocasts
Live Dates/Tours
Conversations with...
Special Offers
Reviews
Contact
Search
Close SearchKeyword
Search
Your cart — Select your cart You have carts in multiple currenciesRemoveItemQuantity × PriceYour cart is emptyTotal — Checkout PRIVACY POLICY NOTICEYour privacy is of the utmost importance to us.It is Gary Husband Online's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to www.garyhusband.com (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "www.garyhusband.com"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and Conditions on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.WEBSITE VISITORSLike most website operators, Gary Husband Online collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Gary Husband Online's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Gary Husband Online's visitors use its website. From time to time, Gary Husband Online may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Gary Husband Online also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on www.garyhusband.com blog posts. Gary Husband Online only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.GATHERING OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATIONCertain visitors to Gary Husband Online's websites choose to interact with Gary Husband Online in ways that require Gary Husband Online to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Gary Husband Online gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to a newsletter at www.garyhusband.com to provide a name and email address.SECURITYThe security of your Personal Information is of great importance to us, but please recognise that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.LINKS TO EXTERNAL SITESOur Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATIONGary Husband Online discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Gary Husband Online's behalf or to provide services available at Gary Husband Online's website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Gary Husband Online's website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Gary Husband Online will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Gary Husband Online discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Gary Husband Online believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Gary Husband Online, third parties or the public at large.EMAIL MARKETING MESSAGES & SUBSCRIPTIONIf you are a registered user of www.garyhusband.com and have supplied your email address, Gary Husband Online may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Gary Husband Online and our products.. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Gary Husband Online takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.Any email marketing messages we send are done so through an EMS, email marketing service provider. An EMS is a third party service provider of software / applications that allows marketers to send out email marketing campaigns to a list of users.Email marketing messages that we send may contain tracking beacons / tracked clickable links or similar server technologies in order to track subscriber activity within email marketing messages. Where used, such marketing messages may record a range of data such as; times, dates, I.P addresses, opens, clicks, forwards, geographic and demographic data. Such data, within its limitations will show the activity each subscriber made for that email campaign.Any email marketing messages we send are in accordance with the GDPR and the PECR. We provide you with an easy method to withdraw your consent (unsubscribe) or manage your preferences / the information we hold about you at any time.Our EMS provider is MailChimp. We may hold the following information about you within our EMS system;Email addressI.P addressSubscription time & dateName if providedAGGREGATED STATISTICSGary Husband Online may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its website. Gary Husband Online may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Gary Husband Online does not disclose your personally-identifying information.COOKIESTo enrich and perfect your online experience, Gary Husband Online uses "Cookies", similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Gary Husband Online uses cookies to help Gary Husband Online identify and track visitors, their usage of www.garyhusband.com, and their website access preferences. Gary Husband Online visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Gary Husband Online's website, with the drawback that certain features of Gary Husband Online's website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Gary Husband Online's use of cookies.E-COMMERCEThose who engage in transactions with Gary Husband Online – by purchasing Gary Husband Online's services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Gary Husband Online collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Gary Husband Online. Gary Husband Online does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.PRIVACY POLICY CHANGESAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Gary Husband Online may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Gary Husband Online's sole discretion. Gary Husband Online encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATIONAll our methods, policies and practices meet the GDPR compliance requirement. Please note that we are exempt from registration in the ICO Data Protection Register because we are only processing personal data for the core business purposes.CREDIT & CONTACT INFORMATIONThis privacy policy was created at https://termsandconditionstemplate.com/privacy-policy-generator/. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy and how we handle user data and personal information, please contact us. This policy is effective as of 14 September 2019.CONSENTBy using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms & Conditions.Gary Husband Online © 2020 PrivacyTermsFollow
Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
